export const chapter = "Chapter - 11: Regional Cultures  ";
export const noOfActivities = 3;

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 1) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Tick the correct option:",
    questions: [
      {
        question: "What is a manifestation of culture, according to the text?",
        optionA: "Food and clothing",
        optionB: "Customs, beliefs, language, literature, and more",
        optionC: "Music and dance",
        correctAnswer: "B",
      },
      {
        question:
          "In the medieval period, how is the culture of India divided?",
        optionA: "Eastern and Western",
        optionB: "Central and regional",
        optionC: "Northern and Southern",
        correctAnswer: "B",
      },
      {
        question:
          "How is the cultural identity of a person in India generally determined?",
        optionA: "By occupation",
        optionB: "By language",
        optionC: "By religion",
        correctAnswer: "B",
      },
      {
        question:
          "What is a significant feature of literature mentioned in the text?",
        optionA: "It reflects the prevailing society and customs.",
        optionB: "It primarily focuses on fictional stories.",
        optionC: "It has no connection to historical events.",
        correctAnswer: "A",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Which language is considered a part of the central culture in the medieval period?",
        optionA: "Marathi",
        optionB: "Bengali",
        optionC: "Sanskrit",
        correctAnswer: "C",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Who patronized painting during the medieval period in India?",
        optionA: "Delhi Sultanate",
        optionB: "Mughal rulers (except Aurangzeb)",
        optionC: "Chola rulers",
        correctAnswer: "B",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Which painting style was influenced by Mughal painting in Rajasthan?",
        optionA: "Rajasthani style",
        optionB: "Kangra style",
        optionC: "Mughal style",
        correctAnswer: "A",
      },
      {
        question:
          "What was a new form of painting expression introduced in the medieval period?",
        optionA: "Mural painting",
        optionB: "Miniature painting",
        optionC: "Abstract painting",
        correctAnswer: "B",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Who is credited with developing a new music style called Quawwali?",
        optionA: "Tansen",
        optionB: "Amir Khusrau",
        optionC: "Aurangzeb",
        correctAnswer: "B",
      },
      {
        question:
          "What did the Cholas assist in the growth of during the medieval period?",
        optionA: "Literature",
        optionB: "Music",
        optionC: "Tamil, Telugu, and Kannada languages",
        correctAnswer: "C",
      },
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 2) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Fill in the blanks:",
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          "The cultural identity of a person in India is often determined by their ___________.",
        optionA: "Occupation",
        optionB: "Language",
        optionC: "Religion",
        correctAnswer: "B",
      },
      {
        question:
          "In the medieval period, literature played a crucial role in reflecting the ___________ of the society.",
        optionA: "Politics",
        optionB: "Economy",
        optionC: "Customs and traditions",
        correctAnswer: "C",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Mughal rulers, with the exception of Aurangzeb, patronized ___________ during the medieval period.",
        optionA: "Sculpture",
        optionB: "Music",
        optionC: "Drama",
        correctAnswer: "B",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The Rajasthani style of painting was deeply influenced by the ___________ style of painting.",
        optionA: "Kangra",
        optionB: "Mughal",
        optionC: "Rajput",
        correctAnswer: "B",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The Cholas assisted in the growth of ___________ languages during the medieval period.",
        optionA: "Sanskrit",
        optionB: "Tamil, Telugu, and Kannada",
        optionC: "Persian and Arabic",
        correctAnswer: "B",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The spread of Hinduism and Buddhism popularized ___________ painting during the medieval period.",
        optionA: "Mural",
        optionB: "Miniature",
        optionC: "Abstract",
        correctAnswer: "B",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The founder of Kannada music during the medieval period is considered to be ___________.",
        optionA: "Tansen",
        optionB: "Purandardas",
        optionC: "Amir Khusrau",
        correctAnswer: "B",
      },
      {
        question:
          "During the medieval period, classical dances like Bharatnatyam and Kathak were considered ___________ types of dance.",
        optionA: "Folk",
        optionB: "Classical",
        optionC: "Traditional",
        correctAnswer: "B",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The Bengali language is greatly influenced by ___________, making it an important literary language.",
        optionA: "Sanskrit",
        optionB: "Urdu",
        optionC: "Persian",
        correctAnswer: "A",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Bengal's architecture in temples is distinctive with its two-roofed (dauchala) or four-roofed (chauchala) structures, imitating the design of temples built in huts with a thatched roof, and its walls were decorated with ___________.",
        optionA: "Frescoes",
        optionB: "Murals",
        optionC: "Sculptures",
        correctAnswer: "C",
      },
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 3) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Write 'True' for True and 'False' for False statements:",
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          "Art finds expression in different ways, such as in writing, painting, music, and sculpture. Rock painting is the earliest example of art.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "True",
      },
      {
        question:
          "With time, new tools came into existence which gave expression to art. When paper was invented, it became easier to dance and draw.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "False",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The invention of the computer has given wings to arts in a big way. New patterns of paintings and pictures have taken a backstage stage.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "False",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The social media has helped to spread the art works to a larger number of people in no time.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "True",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Breaking Away of Barriers in Art: In the past, it was not possible to transmit a piece of art to other cultures and regions easily, so the intercultural impact remained limited.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "True",
      },
      {
        question:
          "This synthesis has its negative aspect too. With mingling of different forms of arts, some people have started to feel that the existence of their unique art forms is being celebrated.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "False",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Literature in the modern period started to express nationalism in different ways and forms. Thus, stories and poetry were composed to motivate people to fight the foreign rule.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "True",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Most of the Indian writers wrote in European languages, and not in English or French.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "False",
      },
      {
        question:
          "In the modern period, painting came to be influenced by current topics, such as social reforms, mythology, politics, etc.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "True",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Different architectural styles such as Hindu, Persian, Mughal, and western made their presence felt in different buildings and monuments in the colonial period.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "True",
      },
    ],
  };
}

export var activityData;
